A Guide to the Hugh L. Robertson Collection, 1948-1983
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 3, Negatives, 1948-1959
  - Sub-series 3-1: Fairfax County Fire Department, 1954-1959
    - Claude Shoop, Fairfax County Fire Department Dispatcher, Portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, Arlington, Va. Junior Optimist Club band marching, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, crowd watching firefighter sliding down rope from extended ladder of Kensington VFD fire truck, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, crowd watching firefighters competing in hose contest, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, Fairfax County Fire Department officials riding in Plymouth Belvedere, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, Fairfax County Fire Marshal's car, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, girls marching in parade, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, girls marching in parade, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, McLean VFD Engine No. 8 Squad Truck, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, McLean VFD firefighters riding in fire engine, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, McLean VFD Ladies Auxiliary marching, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, Mclean VFD Rescue Squad No. 1 Superior Cadillac, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, Naval Gun Factory firefighter float, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, Riverdale VFD firefighters connecting hose to fire engine in competition, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, Riverdale VFD firefighters posing in front of fire engine, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, Riverdale VFD firefighters posing in front of fire engine, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, Riverdale VFD firefighters removing hose from fire engine in competition, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, the National Guard of Honor Drum and Bugle Corps of the American Legion marching, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - D.C. Fire Prevention Parade, trophies displayed on viewing stand, 1954 October 9 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - D.O.A. on Balls Hill Road, body of a man in the bushes, c. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - D.O.A. on Balls Hill Road, body of a man in the bushes, c. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - D.O.A. on Balls Hill Road, close-up of the body, c. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - D.O.A. on Balls Hill Road, view of the crime scene, c. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - D.O.A. on Balls Hill Road, view of the crime scene, c. 1957 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Dunn Loring VFD, front exterior with fire vehicles lined in front [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Dunn Loring VFD, front exterior with fire vehicles lined in front [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Fairfax County Fire Commission dispatcher station, view of fire board, 1955 March 14 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Fairfax County Fire Commission dispatcher station, view of fire board, 1955 March 14 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Fairfax County Fire Commission dispatcher station, view of office and fire board, 1955 March 14 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Fairfax County Fire Commission dispatcher station, view of office and fire board, 1955 March 14 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Fairfax County Fire Department, group looking at map of Fairfax County, L to R: Robert Sullivan, chief dispatcher for Fire services, Moncure “Snuffy” Smith, and Horace Williams, fire dispatcher, Undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Fairfax County Police Department Annandale Substation, exterior, Undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Fairfax VFD, unidentified firefighter posing with girl, Undated (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Jack Feehan, Town of Fairfax Police Department, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Jack Feehan, Town of Fairfax Police Department, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Jack Feehan, Town of Fairfax Police Department, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Jack Feehan, Town of Fairfax Police Department, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Jefferson VFD New Ambulance, close-up of Russell O. Wissinger presenting keys of donated ambulance to firefighters in front of fire station, Undated (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Jefferson VFD New Ambulance, Russell O. Wissinger of Wissinger Chevrolet presenting keys of donated ambulance to firefigthers in front of fire station, Undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Jefferson VFD New Ambulance, Russell O. Wissinger of Wissinger Chevrolet presenting keys of donated ambulance to firefighters in front of fire station, Undated (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Jefferson VFD New Ambulance, Russell O. Wissinger shaking hands with firefighter in front of donated ambulance, Undated (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Lorton VFD, front exterior with vehicles lined in front [3 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - "Mac" McGinley, close-up of injured hand, Undated (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - "Mac" McGinley, close-up of injured hand, Undated (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Map, Master Plan for the Center of McLean [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Map, partial map of Dranesville district, Undated (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Map, partial map of McLean and Tysons Corner, Undated (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Map, Street Plan of Pimmit Hills, Undated (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Map, Street Plan of Pimmit Hills, Undated (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - McLean Carnival, signage with sponsoring local businesses' names [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - McLean Carnival, signage with sponsoring local businesses' names [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - McLean Carnival, signage with sponsoring local businesses' names, Esso gas station in background [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - McLean Carnival, signage with sponsoring local businesses' names, ferris wheel in background [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - McLean Carnival, signage with sponsoring local businesses' names, ferris wheel in background, Undated (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - McLean Carnival, signage with sponsoring local businesses' names, ferris wheel in background, Undated (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - McLean Carnival, signage with sponsoring local businesses' names, Safeway grocery store in background [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - McLean VFD car accident, firefighters gathered around the wreck, Undated (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - McLean VFD car accident, firefighters on the scene, Undated (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - McLean VFD car accident, firefighters on the scene, Undated (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - McLean VFD car accident, firefighters on the scene, Undated (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - McLean VFD car accident, front close-up of wrecked Mercury, Undated (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - McLean VFD car accident, front close-up of wrecked Plymouth, Undated (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - McLean VFD car accident, overturned log truck, Undated (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - McLean VFD car accident, overturned log truck and wrecked Plymouth, Undated (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - McLean VFD car accident, overturned log truck and wrecked Plymouth, Undated (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - McLean VFD car accident, side view of wrecked Mercury, Undated (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - McLean VFD car accident, underside view of overturned log truck, Undated (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - McLean VFD car accident, view of the road, Undated (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - McLean VFD car accident, view of the road, Undated (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - McLean VFD car accident, wrecked Mercury, Undated (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - McLean VFD car accident, wrecked Plymouth, Undated (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - McLean VFD fire engine No. 6, front view of wreckage lying in fire station, Undated (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - McLean VFD fire engine No. 6, overhead view of wreckage lying in fire station, Undated (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - McLean VFD fire engine No. 6, rear view of wreckage lying in fire station, Undated (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - McLean VFD, close-up of "V.F.D. No. 1" decal on fire engine, Undated (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - McLean VFD, fire truck and crew pumping water from pond [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - McLean VFD, fire truck and crew pumping water from pond [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - McLean VFD, fire truck and crew pumping water from pond [2 negatives], Undated (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - McLean VFD, firefighter posing with fire safety students, Undated (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - McLean VFD, firefighter watching over students practicing fire safety techniques, Undated (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - McLean VFD, firefighter watching over students practicing fire safety techniques, Undated (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - McLean VFD, firefighters inspecting squad truck Engine No. 8 in front of fire station, Undated (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - McLean VFD, firefighters inspecting squad truck Engine No. 8 in front of fire station, Undated (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - McLean VFD, firefighters inspecting squad truck Engine No. 8 in front of fire station, Undated (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - McLean VFD, front exterior with fire vehicles lined in front, Undated (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - McLean VFD, Route 123 cedar tree car accident, front of smashed car, 1955 December (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - McLean VFD, Route 123 cedar tree car accident, rescue squad members and county police cluster around the crash site, 1955 December (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - McLean VFD, Route 123 cedar tree car accident, smashed car and cedar tree, 1955 December (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - McLean VFD, Route 123 cedar tree car accident, smashed car hitched on tow truck, 1955 December (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - McLean VFD, Route 123 cedar tree car accident, view of smashed driver's side of car, 1955 December (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Moncure “Snuffy” Smith, dispatcher, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Moncure “Snuffy” Smith, dispatcher, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Annandale fire truck and crowd in front of burning rear north elevation of Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Annandale firefighters using a hose on east side of burning Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, beginning of fire in second story window of rear north elevation of Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Burke firefighter on the ground peeking into smoke-filled doorway in Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Burke firefighter peeking into smoke-filled doorway in Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, children walking in front of south elevation of burning Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, crowd in front of south elevation of burning Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Delbert “Bill” Sheads Fairfax VFD Chief raises hand in front of burning Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, east view of boarded up Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, firefighter brushing off sweat in front of burning Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, firefighter smoking a cigarette pointing in front of burning Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, firefighter walking in front of rear north elevation of Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Franconia fire truck and crowd in front of south elevation of burning Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Franconia fire truck and crowd in front of south elevation of burning Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Ossian Hall burning east view, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Ossian Hall burning front south elevation, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Ossian Hall burning southeast view, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Ossian Hall burning southeast view, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Ossian Hall burning southeast view, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Ossian Hall burning southeast view, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, Ossian Hall colossal portico collapsing, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, smoke billowing out of second-story window of south elevation of Ossian Hall, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, view between trees of firefighters in front of south elevation of Ossian Hall burning, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, view between trees of firefighters in front of south elevation of Ossian Hall burning, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, view between trees of south elevation of Ossian Hall burning, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, view between trees of south elevation of Ossian Hall burning, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - Ossian Hall Training Exercise, view of fire burning inside Ossian Hall through doorway, 1959 September 3 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Pothole, hole on the side of the road, Undated (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Pothole, hole on the side of the road, Undated (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Pothole, two unidentified men measuring pothole on the side of the road, Undated (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Roland Heath, Fairfax County Police Department, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Roland Heath, Fairfax County Police Department, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Roland Heath, Fairfax County Police Department, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, a couple walking from the parking lot, Undated (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride and groom cutting the cake, Undated (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride and groom feeding each other cake, Undated (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride and groom kissing at the altar, Undated (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride and groom posing in front of church, Undated (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride and groom posing with children, Undated (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride and groom posing with others in front of the altar, Undated (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride and groom posing with priest and others in front of the altar, Undated (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride and groom walking down the aisle, Undated (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride posing outside with a woman, Undated (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, bride posing with a man, Undated (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, couple exchanging vows in front of priest, Undated (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, groom wiping forehead with a towel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, groom working on a fire truck, Undated (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, happy couple leaving the church, Undated (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, mother pinning flower on groom, Undated (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, priest bestowing blessing on couple kneeling at the altar, Undated (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, priest handing ring to the bride, Undated (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Saint John's Episcopal Church (Centreville, Va) firefighter wedding, wedding party posing, Undated (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Unidentified firefighters joking around in kitchen, Undated (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Unidentified firefighters joking around in kitchen, Undated (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Unknown smoking building, firefighters climbing ladder of fire truck extended to upper floors, Undated (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Vienna VFD, Bob Hunter and unidentified firefighter holding fire hose nozzle, Undated (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Vienna VFD, Bob Hunter and unidentified firefighter holding fire hose, Undated (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Dewitt Crickenberger showing award to unidentified group, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, firefighters shaking hands in front of cornerstone, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, firefighters speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, firefighters speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, floral arrangements inside bay door, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, furniture and television set donated by Miller & Wren Furniture Co, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, furniture donated by Miller & Wren Furniture Co, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, group of firefighters posing by the cornerstone, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, group of unidentified officials posing inside, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, group of women posing by the cornerstone, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, guests enjoying refreshments, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, invocation prayer, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, invocation prayer, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, line in front of the refreshment table, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, raising of the flag, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill cutting the ribbon, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill presenting Dewitt Crickenberger with service award at podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill shaking hands with firefighter, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill speaking with two unidentified men, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill with Dewitt Crickenberger at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, two firefighters posing by the cornerstone, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified firefighter speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified firefighter speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified man speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified man speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified minister shaking hands with firefighter, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified woman speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of dignitaries, Dewitt Crickenberger, and podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of dignitaries, Rep. Joel Broyhill, and podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of seated crowd, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of seated crowd, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of seating area looking across Center Street, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of seating area looking across Center Street, 1958 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Willis H. Burton, Jr., portrait of Fairfax County's first Fire Marshall, Undated (Box 5, Folder 244)
  - Sub-series 3-2: Washington D.C., Maryland, and Virginia, 1948, Undated
    - Great Falls Park, view of the falls [color negative], Undated (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Meridian Hill Park, Noyes Armillary Sphere and cascade fountain, Undated (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Masonic Lodge (unknown Virginia chapter), group of Freemasons posing, Undated (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Masonic Lodge (unknown Virginia chapter), unidentified man banging gavel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Masonic Lodge (unknown Virginia chapter), unidentified man banging gavel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Silver Spring, Maryland "Avenue of Progress" Celebration, AAA Model T car and clown in parade with Giffords Ice Cream store in the background [color negative], 1948 September 11 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Silver Spring, Maryland "Avenue of Progress" Celebration, marching band and clown in parade alongside Georgia Ave. underpass [color negative], 1948 September 11 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Silver Spring, Maryland "Avenue of Progress" Celebration, ribbon cutting of Georgia Ave. underpass with Charles H. Kopeland, Gov. W. Preston Lane, and B&O Railroad President R.B. White [color negative], 1948 September 11 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Silver Spring, Maryland "Avenue of Progress" Celebration, Two women in dresses riding on the front of the decorated Blossom Shop car float with Giffords Ice Cream store in the background [color negative], 1948 September 11 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Silver Spring, Maryland "Avenue of Progress" Celebration, Veterans of Foreign Wars marching, 1948 September 11 (Box 5, Folder 254)
  - Sub-series 3-3: Family Life, Undated
    - Dead Run Stream?, snow scene, Undated (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Dead Run Stream?, snow scene, Undated (Box 5, Folder 256)